<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hashbang</title><link>https://hashbang.gr/</link><description>Recent content on hashbang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>giannoug</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 14:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hashbang.gr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your Pocket C.H.I.P. plays Pokémon GO better than you</title><link>https://hashbang.gr/turn-your-pocket-chip-into-a-pokemon-go-bot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 14:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hashbang.gr/turn-your-pocket-chip-into-a-pokemon-go-bot/</guid><description>Using bots can ruin the game for others (and you). Don&amp;rsquo;t fight gyms and don&amp;rsquo;t brag about the 2500 CP Dragonite you didn&amp;rsquo;t catch yourself!
My Pocket C.H.I.P. arrived about 10 days ago and still I hadn&amp;rsquo;t figured out anything cool and useful to build with it. During a visit on Reddit, I came across /r/pokemongodev/ and some threads about a Pokémon GO bot. I did some research and decided to try it out on a secondary account.</description></item><item><title>Your own Facebook Messenger bot powered by NodeJS</title><link>https://hashbang.gr/your-own-facebook-messenger-bot-powered-by-nodejs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 21:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hashbang.gr/your-own-facebook-messenger-bot-powered-by-nodejs/</guid><description>A few hours ago Facebook released it&amp;rsquo;s own bot API for the Messenger platform. Nothing fancy like the stuff Microsoft showcased at Build 2016, but it&amp;rsquo;s something. Messenger is used by 900.000.000 people, too. The Messenger bot API is available, ready to be used and the accompanying documentation has been published. You can read the official Facebook Messenger bot getting started guide to help you bootstrap the appropriate Facebook application, pages and permissions.</description></item><item><title>Internet of Things — WiFi-controlled Jester hat for $10</title><link>https://hashbang.gr/wifi-controlled-jester-hat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hashbang.gr/wifi-controlled-jester-hat/</guid><description>Almost a decade ago, it should have been 2003 or 2004 when I was about 11-12 years old, I bought a Jester / Harlequin hat for the Greek &amp;ldquo;Mardi Gras&amp;rdquo;. The hat has eight red LEDs that flash to patterns, which can be switched by a button. The eight red LEDs are controlled by a PCB with a blob of epoxy resin and are powered by two AA batteries. Fast-forward to 2016 a couple of weeks ago, when I decided to replace the PCB with an my own and the red LEDs with RGB one&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>Breaking the fourth wall with Minecraft</title><link>https://hashbang.gr/breaking-the-4th-wall-with-minecraft/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2015 21:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hashbang.gr/breaking-the-4th-wall-with-minecraft/</guid><description>Update 23/11/2015 - I&amp;rsquo;ve got many requests about the WiFi bulbs. You can find them on dx.com. Enjoy!
Recently I started playing Minecraft, again. I find vanilla Minecraft somewhat boring, so I always look out for modpacks. After searching for new modpacks, I stumpled upon FTB Horizons: Daybreaker. Looking at the included mods list, OpenComputers caught my eye.
As the name suggests, OpenComputers adds computers to Minecraft. Real computers!</description></item><item><title>Install Bonjour to Windows without iTunes</title><link>https://hashbang.gr/install-bonjour-to-windows-without-itunes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 12:03:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hashbang.gr/install-bonjour-to-windows-without-itunes/</guid><description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been messing around with Zero-configuration networking (aka Zeroconf) services, mostly because I wish to employ some WiFi modules around the house. There is a problem though, how can I discover what&amp;rsquo;s a device&amp;rsquo;s IP address without poking at the DHCP server&amp;rsquo;s client list and without setting a static IP for each of the modules? I would also prefer to &amp;ldquo;discover&amp;rdquo; such nodes and be able to &amp;ldquo;hot swap&amp;rdquo; them without altering static IPs, MAC addresses and all that stuff.</description></item><item><title>JEY Tech DSO 138 DIY digital oscilloscope kit</title><link>https://hashbang.gr/jey-tech-dso-138-diy-digital-oscilloscope-kit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 13:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hashbang.gr/jey-tech-dso-138-diy-digital-oscilloscope-kit/</guid><description>As I was casually skipping through my emails, I noticed this kit in a Banggood newsletter I received some weeks ago. The JEY Tech DSO 138 DIY digital oscilloscope kit kit was included in a small section with other DIY kits between useless $.99 gadgets, weird Chinese clothes and some $199 8-core multi-SIM smartphones.
Long story short, I purchased most of the kits on the Banggood wholesale shop, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help myself.</description></item><item><title>What a nice Ghost installation you have there!</title><link>https://hashbang.gr/what-a-nice-ghost-installation-you-have-there/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 06:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hashbang.gr/what-a-nice-ghost-installation-you-have-there/</guid><description>It has been almost 7 years since I made my presence known to the Web through my humble and rarely never updated blog. Over the years, my posting rate has been declining as my interest in blogging has worn off. Is it time to make a fresh start with different
This Ghost (screw you WordPress) installation&amp;rsquo;s main responsibility is to help me document my findings in the world of software and hardware engineering, log my progress in different projects and share ideas.</description></item></channel></rss>